PAIGE CLAY

CONTACT

- (L) 0284196940
- paige.clay163@gmail.com
- Invercargill, New Zealand

EDUCATION

NCEA Level 2 with Excellence - Overall Southland Girls High School 2021

NCEA Level 3 with Merit – Calculus Southland Girls High School 2021

Level 4 Certificate of IT EssentialsSouthern Institute of Technology
2022

Bachelor of Information Technology Southern Institute of Technology 2023 - Present

SKILLS & ATTRIBUTES

Communication Analytical
Teamwork Efficient
Critical Thinking Flexible
Time Management Reliable
Comprehension Realistic

ACHIEVEMENTS

1st in Physics, 1st in Digital Technologies, 2nd in Chemistry – High School

2021

Emma Marshall Prize for Excellence with Distinction for 1st in Year 12 - High School

2021

New Zealand Aluminium Prize for Endeavour in Level 2 Sciences - High School

2021

Top JADE Project - SIT

2024

PROFESSIONAL OVERVIEW

I am an IT student with strong customer service and problem-solving skills developed through 5+ years of experience in the supermarket sector. Eager to apply my skills and knowledge in a new role and continue learning and growing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Checkout Supervisor

Pak n Save, Invercargill | 2023 – present

Manage and direct Checkout Department to ensure all operations run smoothly and provide a point of contact for all customer inquiries and complaints to maintain a high level of customer satisfaction.

- Supervise, direct, monitor, and support team members to ensure effective customer service
- Provide Lotto and Café services to customers
- Answer external phone calls, and handle customer complaints and inquires in a friendly and fast manner
- Close up the department at the end of the night, doing up tills, cleaning, ensuring all areas are prepared for the next day

Checkout Operator

Pak n Save, Invercargill | 2019 – 2022

Provide excellent customer service while handling goods and completing transactions in a fast-paced grocery environment.

- Processing card transactions and cash handling
- Quickly responding to customer inquiries and resolving issues to provide customer satisfaction
- Working with Self Service and Shop and Go machines, basic troubleshooting and implementing solutions
- Cleaning and upkeep of customer and staff facilities

REFFEREE

Lisa Hayman

Pak n Save Invercargill Checkout Supervisor 021647527